<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <teiHeader>
      <fileDesc>
         <titleStmt>
            <title>A poem on the coronation of James II of England, Scotland, France, and Ireland, King, defender of the faith</title>
            <author>Willoughby, Stephen, b. 1657 or 8.</author>
         </titleStmt>
         <editionStmt>
            <edition>
               <date>1685</date>
            </edition>
         </editionStmt>
         <extent>Approx. 13 KB of XML-encoded text transcribed from 8 1-bit group-IV TIFF page images.</extent>
         <publicationStmt>
            <publisher>Text Creation Partnership,</publisher>
            <pubPlace>Ann Arbor, MI ; Oxford (UK) :</pubPlace>
            <date when="2011-04">2011-04 (EEBO-TCP Phase 2).</date>
            <idno type="DLPS">A66523</idno>
            <idno type="STC">Wing W2862</idno>
            <idno type="STC">ESTC R9837</idno>
            <idno type="EEBO-CITATION">12590380</idno>
            <idno type="OCLC">ocm 12590380</idno>
            <idno type="VID">63886</idno>
            <availability>
               <p>To the extent possible under law, the Text Creation Partnership has waived all copyright and related or neighboring rights to this keyboarded and encoded edition of the work described above, according to the terms of the CC0 1.0 Public Domain Dedication (http://creativecommons.org/publicdomain/zero/1.0/). This waiver does not extend to any page images or other supplementary files associated with this work, which may be protected by copyright or other license restrictions. Please go to https://www.textcreationpartnership.org/ for more information about the project.</p>
            </availability>
         </publicationStmt>
         <seriesStmt>
            <title>Early English books online.</title>
         </seriesStmt>
         <notesStmt>
            <note>(EEBO-TCP ; phase 2, no. A66523)</note>
            <note>Transcribed from: (Early English Books Online ; image set 63886)</note>
            <note>Images scanned from microfilm: (Early English books, 1641-1700 ; 970:1)</note>
         </notesStmt>
         <sourceDesc>
            <biblFull>
               <titleStmt>
                  <title>A poem on the coronation of James II of England, Scotland, France, and Ireland, King, defender of the faith</title>
                  <author>Willoughby, Stephen, b. 1657 or 8.</author>
               </titleStmt>
               <extent>[6], 8 p.   </extent>
               <publicationStmt>
                  <publisher>Printed by D. Mallet for the author,</publisher>
                  <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
                  <date>1685.</date>
               </publicationStmt>
               <notesStmt>
                  <note>Reproduction of original in Huntington Library.</note>
                  <note>Attributed to Stephen Willoughby. cf. NUC pre-1956.</note>
                  <note>Epistle dedicatory signed: Stephen Willoughby.</note>
               </notesStmt>
            </biblFull>
         </sourceDesc>
      </fileDesc>
      <encodingDesc>
         <projectDesc>
            <p>Created by converting TCP files to TEI P5 using tcp2tei.xsl,
      TEI @ Oxford.
      </p>
         </projectDesc>
         <editorialDecl>
            <p>EEBO-TCP is a partnership between the Universities of Michigan and Oxford and the publisher ProQuest to create accurately transcribed and encoded texts based on the image sets published by ProQuest via their Early English Books Online (EEBO) database (http://eebo.chadwyck.com). The general aim of EEBO-TCP is to encode one copy (usually the first edition) of every monographic English-language title published between 1473 and 1700 available in EEBO.</p>
            <p>EEBO-TCP aimed to produce large quantities of textual data within the usual project restraints of time and funding, and therefore chose to create diplomatic transcriptions (as opposed to critical editions) with light-touch, mainly structural encoding based on the Text Encoding Initiative (http://www.tei-c.org).</p>
            <p>The EEBO-TCP project was divided into two phases. The 25,368 texts created during Phase 1 of the project (2000-2009), initially available only to institutions that contributed to their creation, were released into the public domain on 1 January 2015. The approximately 40,000 texts produced during Phase 2 (2009- ), of which 34,963 had been released as of 2020, originally similarly restricted, were similarly freed from all restrictions on 1 August 2020. As of that date anyone is free to take and use these texts for any purpose (modify them, annotate them, distribute them, etc.). But we do respectfully request that due credit and attribution be given to their original source.</p>
            <p>Users should be aware of the process of creating the TCP texts, and therefore of any assumptions that can be made about the data.</p>
            <p>Text selection was based on the New Cambridge Bibliography of English Literature (NCBEL). If an author (or for an anonymous work, the title) appears in NCBEL, then their works are eligible for inclusion. Selection was intended to range over a wide variety of subject areas, to reflect the true nature of the print record of the period. In general, first editions of a works in English were prioritized, although there are a number of works in other languages, notably Latin and Welsh, included and sometimes a second or later edition of a work was chosen if there was a compelling reason to do so.</p>
            <p>Image sets were sent to external keying companies for transcription and basic encoding. Quality assurance was then carried out by editorial teams in Oxford and Michigan. 5% (or 5 pages, whichever is the greater) of each text was proofread for accuracy and those which did not meet QA standards were returned to the keyers to be redone. After proofreading, the encoding was enhanced and/or corrected and characters marked as illegible were corrected where possible up to a limit of 100 instances per text. Any remaining illegibles were encoded as &lt;gap&gt;s. Understanding these processes should make clear that, while the overall quality of TCP data is very good, some errors will remain and some readable characters will be marked as illegible. Users should bear in mind that in all likelihood such instances will never have been looked at by a TCP editor.</p>
            <p>The texts were encoded and linked to page images in accordance with level 4 of the TEI in Libraries guidelines.</p>
            <p>Copies of the texts have been issued variously as SGML (TCP schema; ASCII text with mnemonic sdata character entities); displayable XML (TCP schema; characters represented either as UTF-8 Unicode or text strings within braces); or lossless XML (TEI P5, characters represented either as UTF-8 Unicode or TEI g elements).</p>
            <p>Keying and markup guidelines are available at the <ref target="http://www.textcreationpartnership.org/docs/.">Text Creation Partnership web site</ref>.</p>
         </editorialDecl>
         <listPrefixDef>
            <prefixDef ident="tcp"
                       matchPattern="([0-9\-]+):([0-9IVX]+)"
                       replacementPattern="http://eebo.chadwyck.com/downloadtiff?vid=$1&amp;page=$2"/>
            <prefixDef ident="char"
                       matchPattern="(.+)"
                       replacementPattern="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/textcreationpartnership/Texts/master/tcpchars.xml#$1"/>
         </listPrefixDef>
      </encodingDesc>
      <profileDesc>
         <langUsage>
            <language ident="eng">eng</language>
         </langUsage>
         <textClass>
            <keywords scheme="http://authorities.loc.gov/">
               <term>James --  II, --  King of England, 1633-1701.</term>
               <term>Coronations --  Poetry.</term>
            </keywords>
         </textClass>
      </profileDesc>
      <revisionDesc>
         <change>
            <date>2010-01</date>
            <label>TCP</label>Assigned for keying and markup</change>
         <change>
            <date>2010-01</date>
            <label>SPi Global</label>Keyed and coded from ProQuest page images</change>
         <change>
            <date>2010-02</date>
            <label>Kayla Ondracek</label>Sampled and proofread</change>
         <change>
            <date>2010-02</date>
            <label>Kayla Ondracek</label>Text and markup reviewed and edited</change>
         <change>
            <date>2010-04</date>
            <label>pfs</label>Batch review (QC) and XML conversion</change>
      </revisionDesc>
   </teiHeader>
   <text xml:lang="eng">
      <front>
         <div type="title_page">
            <pb facs="tcp:63886:1" rendition="simple:additions"/>
            <!-- PDF PAGE 103 -->
            <p>A POEM on the <hi>Corronation</hi> of JAMES II. of <hi>England, Scotland, France,</hi> and <hi>Ire<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>land,</hi> King, <hi>Defender of the Faith.</hi>
            </p>
            <p>
               <hi>LONDON;</hi> Printed by D. Mallet for the <hi>Author,</hi> MDCLXXXV.</p>
         </div>
         <div type="dedication">
            <pb facs="tcp:63886:2"/>
            <!-- PDF PAGE 104 -->
            <pb facs="tcp:63886:2"/>
            <!-- PDF PAGE 104 -->
            <head>The Epiſtle <hi>DEDICATORY:</hi> To the Right Honourable <hi>Francis Lord North,</hi> Baron of <hi>Guilford,</hi> Lord Keeper of the great Scal of <hi>England,</hi> and one of his Majeſties Moſt Hon<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ourable Privy Councel.</head>
            <opener>
               <salute>May it pleaſe your Honour</salute>
            </opener>
            <p>I Am no Relative to thoſe who court univerſal Favours and a flying Fame, with Oſtentation of their own Abili<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ties (though I now appear on a publick Stage) I dare not preſume to contend with any, but content my ſelf in my own <hi>Sphaer,</hi> with my own Language and my own Method, leſt I should ſeem to aſpire higher than I can pretend, or falling too low be loaded with ariſing
<pb facs="tcp:63886:3"/>
               <!-- PDF PAGE 105 -->Wave, and my aſpiring Phantaſie bu<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ry'd in a watery Grave. My <hi>Ambiti<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>on</hi> is only to tell the World that I will tread in the Foot-ſteps of my former <hi>Loyal Anceſtors;</hi> (ſome whereof have ventured both Lives and Fortunes in the lage Rebellion) and that I as well as they, have the ſame abhorrency of Rebels againſt my Prince. I am now under the ſevere Cenſure of the Impar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tial <hi>Critick,</hi> yet I will not diſtruſt the over-ruling Providence of Heaven, but that ſome will excuſe me in what. I have done; and gather Fire from my Coal, to kindle the Noble Flames of Love of <hi>Loyalty</hi> and <hi>Religion.</hi> For as it was with the <hi>Pſalmiſt</hi> ſo it is with me, to abſtain from <hi>Good Words</hi> is Pain and Grief; but if the excellency of all Preſents should always equal the gran<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>deur
<pb facs="tcp:63886:3"/>
               <!-- PDF PAGE 105 -->of thoſe to whom they come, I might juſtly shame or blush at my bold Oblation.</p>
            <p>But being <hi>I</hi> am not unacquainted with ſome part of your Virtues where<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>by <hi>I</hi> am able to give the World a taſt more eaſie to be had in admiration than imitation, <hi>I</hi> preſume upon your <hi>Lord<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſhip</hi>'s Goodneſs. Your <hi>Religion</hi> and <hi>Loyalty,</hi> your <hi>Prudence</hi> and <hi>Learning,</hi> and whatſoever elſe is <hi>Praiſe Worthy,</hi> hath render'd you Eminent in one of the Nobleſt Employs of State wherein you Act with a General applauſe of the whole Realm. But that which gives a Fragrancy to all your <hi>Bed</hi> of <hi>Flowers,</hi> is that humility, which like the <hi>Violet</hi> (though the loweſt yet is the ſweeteſt.) This makes me proſtrate my forlorne Papers at your <hi>Lordſhips Feet,</hi> beſeech<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ing
<pb facs="tcp:63886:4"/>
               <!-- PDF PAGE 106 -->your Goodneſs to condeſcend to the acceptance of theſe poor expreſſions of my reſpects, and to give them your Patronage and Protection, which will shield them from all <hi>Enemies,</hi> and that your happineſs may extend above the reach of all, that you either can deſire or deſerve, is the hearty Prayer of</p>
            <closer>
               <signed>
                  <hi>Your Lordſhip</hi>'s <hi>moſt Faithful and moſt Obedient Servant,</hi> Stephen Willoughby.</signed>
            </closer>
         </div>
      </front>
      <body>
         <div type="poem">
            <pb n="1" facs="tcp:63886:4"/>
            <!-- PDF PAGE 106 -->
            <head>A POEM, on the <hi>CORONATION</hi> of JAMES II, Of <hi>England, Scotland, France, and Ireland,</hi> King, <hi>Defen<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>der of the Faith.</hi> &amp;c.</head>
            <l>
               <hi>ALbion;</hi> unveil thy mourning Shades be dreſs'd,</l>
            <l>With <hi>Lawrel, Charles</hi> thy <hi>Atlas</hi> is at reſt,</l>
            <l>And <hi>James</hi> the Juſt thy <hi>Hercules</hi> is bleſs'd</l>
            <l>With Regal State, now may his Glories run</l>
            <l>A Match with the breath'd Courſes of the Sun.</l>
            <l>Weigh Mirth with Mourning nothing can deſtroy</l>
            <l>Providence repels Ruin from our <hi>Troy,</hi>
            </l>
            <l>Brings Peace, and makes us Citizens of Joy.</l>
            <pb n="2" facs="tcp:63886:5"/>
            <!-- PDF PAGE 107 -->
            <l>The bliſsful Powers of Heaven, deſign'd</l>
            <l>To call the beſt of Kings, and leave behind,</l>
            <l>His Princely Brother in our wavering Iſle,</l>
            <l>To give us equal cauſe to weep and ſmile:</l>
            <l>O happy Man! That hath ſome Grief allow'd,</l>
            <l>Leſt too much Joy ſhould make thy <hi>Brittain</hi> proud.</l>
            <l>Mortal breaches immortal powers repair,</l>
            <l>
               <hi>Elijah</hi> left <hi>Eliſhah</hi> in the Chair-</l>
            <l>Death! Where's thy ſting, in thy Nocturnal Womb?</l>
            <l>No; The Royal Trophies thou haſt made a Tomb:</l>
            <l>Tho' the cold Icy Hands, the Throne or'e-ſpead;</l>
            <l>Wounded the Realm, and touch'd our Monarchs Head,</l>
            <l>Yet not our Peace the Darling of the Dead.</l>
            <l>Tho deeps the Gaſh, behold, here's <hi>Gilead's</hi> Balm,</l>
            <l>Is there a Boiſt'rous Storm a timely Calm?</l>
            <l>Thus Grief and Gladneſs two extreams appear,</l>
            <l>The firſt weighs down, the laſt ſupports me here.</l>
            <l>Revoke thy ſighs the ſhaken <hi>Masbles</hi> cry;</l>
            <l>
               <hi>Scepters</hi> and <hi>Crowns</hi> muſt fall, and <hi>Monarchs</hi> dye;</l>
            <l>They dye to live, and live to riſe on high,</l>
            <l>As Godlike <hi>David,</hi> but <hi>Solomon</hi> is nigh.</l>
            <l>Let ſparkling <hi>Diadems</hi> the Worlds Renown,</l>
            <l>Surround this living Ofspring of a Crown</l>
            <l>Rid on Triumphant Heavens rein ſpire</l>
            <l>The Orbs with language like the <hi>Orphean</hi> Lyre:</l>
            <pb n="3" facs="tcp:63886:5"/>
            <!-- PDF PAGE 107 -->
            <l>To tell the gazing World o're-whelm'd with Care,</l>
            <l>That <hi>April's</hi> Bloſſoms Spring in gentle Air;</l>
            <l>And Flow'rs ſhoot forth 'gainſt new Solemnities</l>
            <l>To deck the Windows of our Paradiſe.</l>
            <l>The Bliſsful Quire Ecchoing ſuch Joys aloud,</l>
            <l>Raviſh'd my Soul, that <hi>I</hi> amongſt the Croud,</l>
            <l>Crept in, to view the Solemn Pomp, and ſee</l>
            <l>Our Monarch ſhining like ſome Deity.</l>
            <l>Gazing about, behold the Noble Train</l>
            <l>Bleſs me! freſh Glorys turn'd my wand'ring Brai<gap reason="illegible" resp="#UOM" extent="1 letter">
                  <desc>•</desc>
               </gap>
            </l>
            <l>My thoughts, I Slep'd or dy'd and roſe again</l>
            <l>So deck'd with Splendours was the Ladys all</l>
            <l>That the Earths Glory ſeem'd Angelical</l>
            <l>Of Royallty ſo darting was the Ray</l>
            <l>That pierc'd my ſoul with joy as well as they</l>
            <l>It Emblemed the Reſurrection day.</l>
            <l>Theſe things ſurpriz'd my dazl'd Senſes, I</l>
            <l>Tranſported was beyond the ſtarry skie</l>
            <l>In Enoch's Chariot to Eternity</l>
            <l>But being loaded with this ſinful duſt</l>
            <l>Ah laſs; I could not wing it with the juſt</l>
            <l>Nor raiſe my Notes to reach the lofty ſtring</l>
            <l>That warbl'd Anthem'd Requiems to the King</l>
            <l>I loos'd the Reins and left the Pompous Throne</l>
            <l>Return'd with gladneſs and ſanck gently down</l>
            <pb n="4" facs="tcp:63886:6"/>
            <!-- PDF PAGE 108 -->
            <l>To find new Royalty adorne our Sphaer</l>
            <l>With Heavenly joys, that by a <hi>Metaphor</hi> are here.</l>
            <l>Then what are they that would have veil'd theſe days,</l>
            <l>And hurl'd Confuſion on great <hi>James</hi>'s Rays?</l>
            <l>Aim'd at the Throne, yet in infernum ſlipt,</l>
            <l>They could not ſoar ſo high their Wings were clipt:</l>
            <l>Their Clamours could not Monarchy deſtroy,</l>
            <l>Only obſtruct an univerſal Joy:</l>
            <l>Miſcreants, our Seraphims immortal Eyes,</l>
            <l>Shines through the Royal Charriot of the Skies;</l>
            <l>To view the Loyal Actions of the Beſt,</l>
            <l>By that the angry Heav'n will know the reſt,</l>
            <l>Seperates their call'd; becauſe they will draw back</l>
            <l>From God, till Hell burſt or the Gibbet Crack.</l>
            <l>Sometimes like <hi>Judas,</hi> they'll appear to be</l>
            <l>True Proteſtants to <hi>James</hi> and <hi>Monarchy.</hi>
            </l>
            <l>Pay Homage to the Royal Heir alone,</l>
            <l>Leave him with Swords and Staves a deadly Groan,</l>
            <l>Demoliſh'd Scepter and a ruin'd Throne,</l>
            <l>But Monſters; why ſo cruel to defeat,</l>
            <l>Majeſty ſo legitimately great.</l>
            <l>Their tott'ring Noddles are ſtifled with fears,</l>
            <l>Anxieties and doubts their blear-ey'd with Tears,</l>
            <l>Trumpets and Drums ſtikes terrours in their Ears</l>
            <pb n="5" facs="tcp:63886:6"/>
            <!-- PDF PAGE 108 -->
            <l>Leſt piercing crys of Blood ſhould ſeem to rend</l>
            <l>The Skies for Judgment on his Fathers End:</l>
            <l>Whoſe Princely Head mourn'd under the black Yoak</l>
            <l>And ſtrangely ſtrangled with a fatal Stroke.</l>
            <l>Oh tell it not in <hi>Gath,</hi> nor let it come</l>
            <l>Into the publick Streets of <hi>Askelon.</hi>
            </l>
            <l>Direful! let not the Sober Heathen ſee,</l>
            <l>Pagans will bluſh at ſuch Impiety.</l>
            <l>If Nature mean to cleanſe her Magazin</l>
            <l>From all Sedition ſhe muſt firſt begin</l>
            <l>To root out Errour that unſeen let in</l>
            <l>Rebellion; that ſame Leproſie of Sin.</l>
            <l>Faction Tranſport, or let the hung'ry Wave,</l>
            <l>ſwallow Rebels in one diſcenting Grave.</l>
            <l>What if the Conqu'ring Sword or <hi>Nero's</hi> Rod,</l>
            <l>Should ſtain the Corners of the Land with Blood</l>
            <l>They'r juſt Scourges of a diſpleaſed God.</l>
            <l>In <hi>Rome</hi> Belov'd <hi>Berenice</hi> muſt not Reign</l>
            <l>While Roman Hatred, Envy and diſdain,</l>
            <l>The Royal <hi>Titus,</hi> and his Honour ſtain:</l>
            <l>For he befor he Reign'd with Luxury,</l>
            <l>Was charg'd with Auvarice and Cruelty,</l>
            <l>
               <gap reason="illegible" resp="#UOM" extent="1 letter">
                  <desc>•</desc>
               </gap>he Senate fear'd a <hi>Nero</hi>'s <hi>Tyrany.</hi>
            </l>
            <pb n="6" facs="tcp:63886:7"/>
            <!-- PDF PAGE 109 -->
            <l>But his ſweeet Prudent Government of things,</l>
            <l>Wip'd off Aſperſions, he the beſt of Kings</l>
            <l>A Mirrour of Monarchs through <hi>Rome</hi> was wrote,</l>
            <l>Mankinds Delight's an Eidemick Vote.</l>
            <l>
               <hi>Jeruſ'lem's</hi> Conqueſt ſpread abroad his Fame</l>
            <l>Tho' the beſieged wallow'd in a Flame,</l>
            <l>His pitty Marbl'd an Eternal Name:</l>
            <l>Whoſe tender Eyes water'd his Cheeks with Dews.</l>
            <l>To ſee the burnings of the ſtubborn Jews.</l>
            <l>'Tis true we've no <hi>Jeruſ'lem</hi> but a Rout,</l>
            <l>Of Hect'ring Jews like <hi>Phariſees</hi> about</l>
            <l>That would aſperſe ſincerity of State</l>
            <l>With Subtil Calumny that came too late:</l>
            <l>But ſure we are, his lofty mind is free</l>
            <l>From the leaſt Charge of hated Cruelty</l>
            <l>And we'l depend upon his Clemency.</l>
            <l>A <hi>Temple</hi> to this <hi>Hero</hi> let our Land</l>
            <l>Each City be an <hi>Altar</hi> ar command,</l>
            <l>And ev'ry Man a Statue to ſet forth</l>
            <l>His Noble Acts and truly Royal Worth.</l>
            <l>As Majeſty ſits in his ſacred Face</l>
            <l>So mercy the Derivative of his Race,</l>
            <l>Is no leſs ſplendent in his Acts of Grace:</l>
            <pb n="7" facs="tcp:63886:7"/>
            <!-- PDF PAGE 109 -->
            <l>Gaze on his brave Atchievements they'l command,</l>
            <l>Active Obedience from a ſinful Land;</l>
            <l>Once from Invaſion's ranſom'd with his hand.</l>
            <l>They were no Grapples of a <hi>Cyclop</hi>'s <hi>Arms,</hi>
            </l>
            <l>No nor deluding <hi>Syren's</hi> canting Charms</l>
            <l>That could ſurprize the Famous <hi>Graecian,</hi> he</l>
            <l>Paſs'd by <hi>Charibdis</hi> and <hi>Mortality:</hi>
            </l>
            <l>Unmask the Tragick Scene that once o're ſpread</l>
            <l>Our Brittiſh Vallies with a Forreign dread</l>
            <l>Of horrid Ruine Epidemical,</l>
            <l>Had not our Famous <hi>James</hi> high Admiral,</l>
            <l>With Courage trampl'd on the Deep and ſtood</l>
            <l>A Valient Victor in a Sea of blood.</l>
            <l>Furniſh'd with Wiſdom as a Warriour ought</l>
            <l>To be he Steers his Courſe for Triump, Fought</l>
            <l>To defend's Right, and ſhield his Brother's Crown</l>
            <l>From Invaders, now th' <hi>Martial Camp</hi>'s his own.</l>
            <l>Thus <hi>Agamemnon</hi> Stout, (as Poets feign,)</l>
            <l>If ten (like <hi>Neſtor</hi>) <hi>Councellours</hi> remain</l>
            <l>With <hi>Conqueſt</hi> would have breath'd a <hi>Trojan</hi> vein.</l>
            <l>And the World's <hi>Conqu'rour</hi> would enrich his Head</l>
            <l>With the ſurviving Libraries of the Dead.</l>
            <l>To ſhow that Policy the Learned Pen</l>
            <l>Marbles above the common force of Men.</l>
            <pb n="8" facs="tcp:63886:8"/>
            <!-- PDF PAGE 110 -->
            <l>
               <hi>Champion,</hi> thrice welcome let thy fragrant breath,</l>
            <l>Inſpire Dominions with a Second Birth</l>
            <l>Of Gladneſs, thou'rt the <hi>Cherub</hi> of the Earth.</l>
            <l>Only with Virtues ſeed <hi>Agrippa</hi>'s breath</l>
            <l>Could make <hi>Octavians</hi> body bleſſed Earth:</l>
            <l>In vain's th' Attempt whilſt Heaven's Golden Show'rs</l>
            <l>Of Grace Bloſſoms the ſacred Plant with Flow'rs;</l>
            <l>The Fruit's for none but Immortal Pow'rs.</l>
            <l>Tis no ſuch Fruit as ſow'r'd our Fathers Age,</l>
            <l>Elſe why with Swords ſhould <hi>Seraphims</hi> Engage,</l>
            <l>To Guard our <hi>Sion</hi> from uſurping Rage.</l>
            <closer>VIVAT REX.</closer>
            <trailer>FINIS</trailer>
         </div>
      </body>
      <back>
         <div type="order">
            <p>Enter'd according to <hi>Order.</hi>
            </p>
            <pb facs="tcp:63886:8"/>
            <!-- PDF PAGE 110 -->
         </div>
      </back>
   </text>
</TEI>
